http://www.powerballs.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
RPM Sports Ltd (“RPM Sports”) directly operates several Internet sites for the purpose of selling products and associated accessories under the Powerball®, NSD®, NSD Power®, NSD Powerball™, NSD Power ball™ and Powerspin® brands. Additionally RPM Sports operates said Internet sites for the purpose of promoting and selling complementary products and offering a resource for information to their customers. It also offers a submission facility whereby site users can submit their high score information, testimonials, stories, images and/or questions and comments regarding the RPM Sports range of products and bands and their use for display on the site. By using any of the features of the site or accessing content, you agree that any information which you submit will be archived by RPM Sports and will be made available to site users and RPM Sports agents at the sole discretion of RPM Sports.
Please note
We collect limited personal information and archive your data pertaining to you securely.
We will never rent, sell or share information that personally identifies you for marketing purposes.
We may occasionally contact you via email regarding new products and or services and other brand news. If we do happen to send a newsletter, then you will be given the opportunity to safely and permanently exclude yourself from future mailings and at no cost.
Personal information
When you submit to the Testimonials, Affiliate, Score submission, Image submission, Story submission, Discussion Forum and/or Ordering facility, you will be asked to supply some personal information including your Name, Country, and depending on the area submitted to, your Address, Email and Telephone details. Your details are stored securely by RPM Sports and/or by its service providers and will only be used in a manner to which you have agreed.
Payment details are not entered directly on the RPM Sports site – only through third-party providers.
Ways in which your data is stored:
By RPM Sports: On its servers in Ireland and in server backups maintained at its premises in Ireland. RPM Sports may hold your name, address, telephone, and email address, as well as images/content submitted to the site as well as details of any orders you have placed including payment transaction confirmations – RPM Sports, have no access to your private payment information (credit card numbers etc)
By PayPal/Stripe: On their servers in Europe and the USA as well as other cloud-based locations and in line with their privacy policies. Payment providers may store your name, address, telephone number and email address as well as card details in an encrypted format in order to enable them to securely process payments using your chosen method.
By MailChimp: On their cloud-based servers around the world and in line with their privacy policy. MailChimp has access to your name, email address, country and the currency in which you purchased previously from RPM Sports in order to enable us to send targeted newsletters to you.
By Couriers/Shipping companies: RPM Sports will provide your name, address and if applicable telephone and email contact information to couriers and other shipping providers to enable them to safely deliver your order to you.
RPM Sports takes the security of your information very seriously and takes all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is not accessed inappropriately. All databases and administrative interfaces are password protected and are accessed only by authorised persons through a secure connection.
Payment information
During the ordering process, you are required to enter your credit card or other payment details in order to successfully complete the transaction. RPM Sports use PayPal and Stripe as our payments partners who handle the payments aspect of the ordering process in their own secure environments. At no time during or subsequent to the transaction will RPM Sports do not have access to your credit card details, and only store a payment reference issued by the payment provider for payments tracking.
When you sign up as an affiliate with RPM Sports, you are required to provide your PayPal account details. These details are used for the sole purpose of transmitting electronically any commission due to RPM Sports affiliate partners.
Email Contact
RPM Sports will occasionally send marketing and other communications to you.
Where an order is placed with the company, we will contact you in connection with your order only to update you on progress and to confirm shipping as required or if there is a problem with your order details.
Where permission has been granted for us to send marketing and other emails to you we will do so in accordance with your consent. With each marketing email, you will have the option to unsubscribe from future communications of this nature.
Other information
Where any other information is included in any submissions to our website, we guarantee that this information will be used only for the purpose of improving the service provided to you and to provide enhancements to our site, where necessary, based on the information provided.
RPM Sports will never sell, rent or share your personal information, including your personal and/or contact information, with any external parties for any purpose unless required to do so by law.
When we may disclose your personal information
We will not disclose your personally identifying information to third parties unless we believe we are required to do so by law or have a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (b) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (c) respond to requests for information or technical support, or (d) protect the rights, property or safety of RPM Sports, its agents and other users.
For further information on any of the above, please contact us.
